<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<articles>
    <article>
    	<id>1</id>
    	<author>John Doh</author>
    	<tag>Sport</tag>
    	<date>1/3/2014</date>
    	<title>Something Something Wins League</title>
    	<text>  Brend Rod was in no mood for mind games following Blahblah draw with blah Palace on Monday. 
    	Rod effectively conceded the 2013-14 A-League title to Something Something City during a postgame interview. 
    	The blahblah manager said he expects Something Something City to win its last two games and end his team’s dreams of domestic glory.
    	 “Yea, there’s no doubt,” Rod said. “I think will go on and win it. We needed to win tonight to have any sort of chance to keep the 
    	 pressure on going into the last game, and we didn’t do that. It’s bitterly disappointing.” Blahblah conceded three goals 11 minutes 
    	 late in the second half against Something Palace. The wild, 3-3 draw gave the Reds a one-point lead atop the A-League standings, 
    	 but Something City has two games (both at home) remaining and a healthy lead in goal differential. Blah still has a mathematical 
    	 chance of winning its first league title since 1990, but it would take a monumental collapse on Something Something City’s part 
    	 for that to happen. Rod could have stayed coy or even falsely positive, but he called the A-League title race like he sees it.</text>
    </article>
    
    <article>
    	<id>2</id>
    	<author>Jack Sparrow</author>
    	<tag>Games</tag>
    	<date>1/2/2014</date>
    	<articlename>Tiger Telematics Back In Bussiness, Stefan Eriksson New CEO</articlename>
    	<text>  Stefan Eriksson and two other Swedish Gizmondo Europe executives are back in business and promise a new better console
    	In November 2007, Carl Freer stated in an interview with the Swedish-American journalist Hans Sandberg that he was interested 
    	in starting up production of the Gizmondo again.[8] In April 2008, a press release was issued that an agreement had been reached 
    	between the joint liquidators of Gizmondo Europe Ltd in Liquidation and one of the company's ex-Directors, Carl Freer. 
    	The press release originated as a low quality copy of a letter purported to be from one of the accounting firms handling the insolvency, 
    	posted to a file sharing site. According to Mr Freer, “the shareholders of Tiger Telematics will now be able to prosper on the 
    	re-introduction of the Gizmondo into the market.</text>
    </article>
    
    <article>
    	<id>3</id>
    	<author>John Doh</author>
    	<tag>Sport</tag>
    	<date>11/1/2014</date>
    	<title>Something Lose League</title>
    	<text>  Something manager Johan De Beer believes Something City will lose the A-League title but said his side had s ready to play.
While Perth-lag has proved an issue for some teams this season, Scott backed his conditioning staff to manage his players for Sunday’s clash against Gold Coast at Etihad Stadium.
The fifth-placed Kangaroos have a nine-day turnaround to recover from their 13-point win over Fremantle on Anzac Day.
“When you win you come back a lot better, let me tell you, and we haven’t experienced that too often,’’ Scott said yesterday. </text>
    </article>
</articles>